http://www.sciowa.org/privacy/

OPEN THURSDAYS, SATURDAYS, SUNDAYS & SELECT DATES: Due to capacity restrictions, we recommend reserving advance tickets for either 9:00 am-12:00 pm or 1:00-4:00 pm. Face coverings are required for all visitors ages 2 and up. Learn more about our COVID-19 safety precautions and what to expect during your visit. Read More
Privacy
Home
Privacy
The Science Center of Iowa and Blank IMAX Dome Theater privacy statement covers our Web site, located at http://www.sciowa.orgAccess to Our Web Site The Science Center of Iowa and Blank IMAX Dome Theater is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our Web site. You are free to access and browse our site without disclosing personal data, and you can be assured that we endeavor to protect the confidentiality and security of your information at all times.We do not release any information to outside parties without the express permission of our Web site users.Information Collection The Science Center of Iowa and Blank IMAX Dome Theater does not automatically collect personal information from our Web site nor do we use cookies to store personal information. We do not link personal information about specific individuals with any other information we collect, either on our Web site or in our facilities.We do not collect personal information from other sources such as public records or private databases nor do we release or sell personal information about those who access our Web site.We do collect personal information that is voluntarily provided while using our services or affiliates. All privacy practices and regulations apply to this information, as well.Confidentiality and Security The Science Center of Iowa and Blank IMAX Dome Theater does not disclose personal information to other organizations. We ensure that personal information will not be disclosed to federal or state institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.If donating to The Science Center of Iowa and Blank IMAX Dome Theater you may be recognized with first and last name mention.We have instituted technical measures to protect personal information in our files from unauthorized access; improper use or disclosure; unauthorized modification, or unlawful destruction or accidental loss.All Science Center of Iowa and Blank IMAX Dome Theater employees who have access to and who process personal information are obligated to maintain the confidentiality of the information.Our Web site does provide access to additional information with links to other sites. It is our hope that these sites offer privacy protection, but The Science Center of Iowa and Blank IMAX Dome Theater is not responsible for their content or privacy practices.Privacy TermsScience Center of Iowa and Blank IMAX Dome Theater may revise these Terms at any time without notice by updating this posting. Your continued use of the Site after such modifications have been made will constitute your acceptance of such revised Terms.
Home
Today’s Schedule
Visit
Planning Your Visit
Get Tickets
Hours & Admission
Directions & Parking
Schools & Groups
What On Earth?
When Things Get Moving
Why The Sky?
